[  
  {
    "question": "Why We Use <br> Element?",
    "a": "To Make Text Bold",
    "b": "To Make Text Italic",
    "c": "To Add Breakline",
    "d": "To Create Horizontal Line",
    "correct": "c"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is <img> Element Has Attribute href?",
    "a": "Yes",
    "b": "No Its For Anchor Tag <a>",
    "c": "All Elements Has This Attribute",
    "d": "Answer 1 And 3 Is Right",
    "correct": "b"
  },
  {
    "question": "How Can We Make Element Text Bold?",
    "a": "Putting It Inside <b> Tag",
    "b": "Putting It Inside <strong> Tag",
    "c": "Customizing It With Font-Weight Property In CSS",
    "d": "All Answers Is Right",
    "correct": "d"
  },
  {
    "question": "What Is The Right Hierarchy For Creating Part Of Page?",
    "a": "<h2> Then <p> Then <h1> Then <p> Then <h3> Then <p> Then <img>",
    "b": "<h1> Then <p> Then <h3> Then <p> Then <h2> Then <p> Then <img>",
    "c": "<h2> Then <p> Then <h3> Then <p> Then <h1> Then <p> Then <img>",
    "d": "All Solutions Is Wrong",
    "correct": "d"
  },
  {
    "question": "How Can We Include External Page Inside Our HTML Page?",
    "a": "By Using Include in HTML",
    "b": "By Using Load In HTML",
    "c": "By Using iFrame Tag",
    "d": "All Solutions Is Wrong",
    "correct": "c"
  },
  {
    "question": "What Is The Tag That Not Exists in HTML?",
    "a": "<object>",
    "b": "<basefont>",
    "c": "<abbr>",
    "d": "All Tags Is Exists in HTML",
    "correct": "d"
  },
  {
    "question": "How We Specify Document Type Of HTML5 Page?",
    "a": "<DOCTYPE html>",
    "b": "<DOCTYPE html5>",
    "c": "<!DOCTYPE html5>",
    "d": "<!DOCTYPE html>",
    "correct": "d"
  },
  {
    "question": "What Is The Element Thats Not Exists in HTML5 Semantics?",
    "a": "<article>",
    "b": "<section>",
    "c": "<blockquote>",
    "d": "<aside>",
    "correct": "c"
  },
  {
    "question": "In HTML Can We Use This Way To Add Attributes?",
    "a": "<div class='class-name'>",
    "b": "<div class=class-name>",
    "c": "<div class=\"class-name\">",
    "d": "All Is Right",
    "correct": "d"
  },
  {
    "question": "In HTML Can We Use This Way To Add Attributes?",
    "a": "<div class='class-name'>",
    "b": "<div class=class-name>",
    "c": "<div class=\"class-name\">",
    "d": "All Is Right",
    "correct": "d"
  },{
    "question": "In HTML Can We Use This Way To Add Attributes?",
    "a": "<div class='class-name'>",
    "b": "<div class=class-name>",
    "c": "<div class=\"class-name\">",
    "d": "All Is Right",
    "correct": "d"
  }]